(Leonard:)Tell you what--
the surgery's not for a week,
(Leonard:)I'll think about it.
(Sheldon:)Thank you. And while
you're thinking about it,
(Sheldon:)if you have the surgery
in Nicaragua during
(Sheldon:)monsoon season,
I can practically
(Sheldon:)guarantee your death.
(Raj(on phone):)Yes. Okay.
I-I understand.
(Raj(on phone):)Of course, yes.
(Raj(on phone):)I'll call you tomorrow.
(Raj(on phone):)Bye.
(Howard:)So I found this fencing school
in Burbank
(Howard:)that has a Jedi class.
(Howard:)And if you're cool
being the only adults there,
(Howard:)they said they are.
(Raj:)Dude, my parents just split up.
What?!
Uh, that was my dad
on the phone.
(Raj:)He moved out.
(Howard:)Oh, my God, I... I'm sorry.
(Howard:)I mean, if you're not up to it,
we don't have to go out,
(Howard:)we can just hang here.
No,
(Raj:)it's fine.
It's not that big a deal.
(Raj:)As long as they're happy,
I'm happy.
(Raj:)And when I get to see them
for the holidays,